





## **Important**

· Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

# Summary

Jump to Section

Talented System Administrator focused on performance optimization and technical improvements with an understanding of cost-effective decision making and usability. Certified in MCSA and 4 years of experience in large-scale distributed network environments.

#### **Work Experience**

Shanthi Gears (Net Access India Ltd) as System Engineer May 2019 to Nov 2020

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Shanthi Gears Limited (Net Access India Ltd), Coimbatore, Tamil Nadu Create and manage users in active directory. Maintain Qnap file server and give access to a user through AD. Symantec antivirus server installation and

configuration. OS deployment in Citrix VM & Windows Hyper-V.

Install software through group policy.

Screen saver change in group policy.

Daily backup and weekly tape backup using CA Arc serve

Install and configure Creo, Auto Desk, KISSsoft,

Solidworks, Oracle

Thunderbird and outlook mail configure. Video conference, Teams and Skype support.

Update windows patches using WSUS serve. Domain user account unlock and reset

password. Troubleshoot network issue and access point configure.

Coordinate with firewall team to give the web site access.

Coordinate with vendor for hardware issue. Configuring Pinter like dot matrix, LaserJet, and Rico Xerox machine

Configure Office 365 subscription like F3,E1, & E3

TI Cycles Of India (Net Access India Ltd) as System Engineer Jul 2018 to May 2019

Manage and configure Symantec antivirus

3CI VC.

Configure Network license for Designing

software in the server.

Install and configure Adobe CC, Creo, Coral Draw, Rhino, Key Shot, Auto Desk.

Create a new user ld in active directory and

manage users and computers. Troubleshoot and configure outlook.

Managing assets using Manage engine and Sapphire.

Troubleshoot network issues in switches and

configure Wi-Fi Routes. Configure static Internet Protocol to laptops

and desktop.

Create Item code for laptop, desktop parts in

Mdas (Master Data Management).

Call log Dell and HP for warranty clime also on

call basic.

Follow-up vendors for hardware issues in laptops, desktops, and printers.

Configure Forti client and Windows VPN for

Laptop users.

#### Jumbo Electronics as IT Engineer Nov 2017 to Feb 2018

Installing Biometric device driver in HP tablets.

Troubleshooting operating system and

hardware issues

Replace defective parts in laptop and desktop. Deploying the operating system in laptop and

desktop.

Give support for HP and Lenovo products, like

all in one desktop and laptops.

# Infosys as System Engineer

Apr 2016 to Aug 2017

Managing and Maintaining the IT Infrastructure

Management and the core activities like

Performing system administration job on Windows Servers and Desktops.

Experience of working on the highest priority Incident tickets with high critical deadlines.

Installation of Windows7, 8.1, 10, server 2008 and 2012 Operating Systems.

Installing and Configuring the Printers.

Coordinating with the network team for VLAN Changes & connectivity issues.

Replace defective parts in laptop and desktop.

Call logs defective parts for Acer Desktops.

Deploying Laptop and enabling bit locker key for the drives.

^ Back to Top

# **Education**

#### UG: B.Tech/B.E. (electronics and communication engineering) from Macro Collage Of Engineering Technology, Valliyur in 2015

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs: Microsoft Certified Solution Associate **Technical Support Fundamentals** 

^ Back to Top

### **IT Skills**

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Advanced Help Desk (AHD)			
Call Tracker System (CTS)			
WINDOWS OS			
MS-OFFICE			
AD			
CITRIX			
DHCP			
DNS			
Azure Admin			
SYMANTEC			
ADFS			
GROUP POLICY			
HYPER-V			
Office 365			
оил оок			

ı	0012001
	Share Point
	WSUS

^ Back to Top

# Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
english				
tamil				

^ Back to Top

#### **Affirmative Action**

Work Authorization

Category: **General**Physically Challenged: **No** 

Employment Status: Full time

Job Type: Permanent

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.